AYAZ ZAFAR

TIPTON, UNITED KINGDOM

O7465 206505 ayaziqbalzafar@gmail.com

(f) https://ayazzafar.com in https://linkedin.com/in/ayaz-zafar



About Me

A highly motivated and hardworking individual, who has experience in IT & in Pharmacy Dispensing. I work exceptionally well in a team both as a leader and a follower as I believe that great companies are built on teamwork and cooperation.

Experience

I-Dispense | June 2022 - Present

Pharmacy Dispenser

Receive and store medications coming into the pharmacy, maintain stock of prescription medications, keep records and maintain an inventory of drugs to facilitate the role of a

JD Sports | Nov 2021 - Jan 2022

Sales Assistant

Greeting Customers as they enter the store and as they leave, Keeping the store well maintained, Helping Customers by asking, them if they need any help.

Appstack | Dec 2020 - Apr 2021

Web Developer

- · Designing Websites and Apps
- · Maintain and Update Websites
- Experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and other relevant Web Design Coding Language

Education

Dudley College of Technology | Sep 2022 - Present

Systems Support for IT Technicians Diploma - Level 3

- Customer Support Provision Networking Principles
- Maintain Equipment & Systems Install & Configure Networks
- Install & Configure Software Acquisition & Delivery ICT Support & System
- · Repair Centre Procedures

Dudley College of Technology | Sep 2021 - Jun 2022

Systems Support for IT Technicians Diploma - Level 2

- · Customer Support Provision · Networking Principles
- Maintain Equipment & Systems Install & Configure Networks
- Software Installation Testing Equipment Systems and Data Security
- Repair Centre Procedures Visual Basic

Leasowes High School | Sep 2016 - Jun 2021

GCSE, Computer Science

School of Coding | Nov 2020 - Feb 2021

Training, Web Developer

- Coding
- · Designing Websites
- · Python, HTML, CSS & JavaScript

Qualifications

Level 2 Diploma in ICT Systems and Principles for IT Professionals

Buttercups Level 2 Pharmacy Dispenser